[
  {
    "question": "How many yellow cards have occurred so far?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 0",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 2",
      "D. 3"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      5
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has received more yellow cards up to now?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams",
      "D. Neither team"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      5
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player received the last yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Sadio Mane",
      "B. Trent Alexander-Arnold",
      "C. Simon Mignolet",
      "D. None"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      5
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total yellow cards occurred in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 1",
      "B. 2",
      "C. 3",
      "D. 4"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      12,
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most yellow cards in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams",
      "D. Neither team"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      12,
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Who were all the players involved in yellow cards?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Sadio Mane, Trent Alexander-Arnold",
      "B. Sadio Mane, Simon Mignolet",
      "C. Sadio Mane, Trent Alexander-Arnold, Simon Mignolet",
      "D. None"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      12,
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more yellow cards in this match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      12,
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams",
      "D. Neither team"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      12,
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Sadio Mane",
      "B. Trent Alexander-Arnold",
      "C. Simon Mignolet",
      "D. None"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      12
    ],
    "current_event_index": 5,
    "index": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "How many yellow cards have occurred so far?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 1",
      "B. 2",
      "C. 3",
      "D. 4"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      12
    ],
    "current_event_index": 12,
    "index": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has received more yellow cards up to now?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams",
      "D. Neither team"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      12
    ],
    "current_event_index": 12,
    "index": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player received the last yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Sadio Mane",
      "B. Trent Alexander-Arnold",
      "C. Simon Mignolet",
      "D. None"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      12
    ],
    "current_event_index": 12,
    "index": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more yellow cards in this match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": 12,
    "index": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams",
      "D. Neither team"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": 12,
    "index": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Sadio Mane",
      "B. Trent Alexander-Arnold",
      "C. Simon Mignolet",
      "D. None"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": 12,
    "index": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "How many yellow cards have occurred so far?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 2",
      "B. 3",
      "C. 4",
      "D. 5"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      12,
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": 18,
    "index": 15
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has received more yellow cards up to now?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Opponent",
      "C. Both teams",
      "D. Neither team"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      12,
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": 18,
    "index": 16
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player received the last yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Sadio Mane",
      "B. Trent Alexander-Arnold",
      "C. Simon Mignolet",
      "D. None"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      12,
      18
    ],
    "current_event_index": 18,
    "index": 17
  }
]